[somber instrumental music playing]
WE DON'T NEED APPS.
ENROLL MORE SLUTS LIKE CHLOE.
MY ATTENTION SPAN SUCKS.
CAN I GET A SCRIPT FOR THAT?
[Luis sighs]
They're mostly trolling each other.
That's all.
If they aren't going to ask for help,
it's not effective.
Nor is my job.
I see. Well, we just launched the app.
We need to give it a bit more time.
[speaking inaudibly]
[Omar sighs]
- Okay.
- [door opens]
[indistinct chatter]
[cell phone chimes]
[cell phone beeps]
[Mateo] Omar, I respect the fact
that you wanted to quit therapy.
I just feel it's worth stating,
I believe we still had a ways to go
and that you don't need
to go back on medication.
Let alone go back on it on your own.
I'm here for you if you need me.
- [cell phone chimes]
- Hello, Mateo. How're you doing?
Honestly, I just needed a break
from therapy.
That's all. But thanks for your concern.
Means a lot.
[cell phone beeps]
[sighs deeply]
[ominous music playing]
[music swells]
- [Omar panting]
- [sounds distort]
- [Omar, echoing] Samuel!
- [Rebe] Samuel!
What the hell did he do to you?
- [high-pitched ringing]
- [Omar breathing shakily]
- [Omar, echoing] Samuel? Samuel.
- [thunder rumbles]
[ominous music building]
- [ringing]
- [Omar, crying] Samuel.
[thunder crashes overhead]
[Omar exhales]
[continues panting]
[tense music pulsing]
[water running]
[faucet stops]
[music fades slowly]
[sobs]
[unsettling instrumental music playing]
- [music fades slowly]
- [vending machine beeps]
[indistinct chatter]
- [Iván] Hey.
- Hey.
What you got there?
Your outfit. For the race.
Take it. It's yours.
What do you mean? No fuckin' way.
Joel, just a gift from a friend.
Right. And so is paying
for my tuition to come here?
[scoffs] No, Iván. No.
But without a suit,
you won't be allowed to attend.
Well, don't you worry about that.
I wasn't even planning on going.
Don't have the money for it.
Joel.
Honestly, I'd love to go with you
and just have a good time together.
["Underneath the Sun" by JFDR playing]
And you knew my size, how?
I didn't. Educated guess.
- Yeah. [inhales sharply]
- ♪ A drink to the mishaps… ♪
I'll go try it on, and we can see
just how sharp your eyes are.
I'm off to the locker room.
♪ Another, for the instance… ♪
Coming? That way,
you'll see if it fits, right?
♪ A soft kiss for the sorrys ♪
♪ And the deeds never undone ♪
♪ And a prayer for the truth ♪
♪ Whether it saves you or faults ♪
- Something the matter?
- [Iván] With me? No.
Nothing's wrong.
- [Joel laughs] Okay.
- [Iván] Nothing. [chuckles]
No, nothing.
What could be wrong? [laughs]
Hi.
[song fades]
[tense music playing]
[Iván] Omar? [laughs]
Shit, Iván.
- [Iván] Fuck.
- Been forever.
[Iván] How are you, huh?
[chuckles] What're you doin' here?
[tense music building]
I see you've met my boyfriend.
You know each other?
So, what are you doin' here?
I'm just, um…
There's a charity race comin' up,
so I'm tryin' on a suit.
What about you? What're you doin' here?
CHARITY HORSE RACE
[indistinct chatter]
- Morning, Roberta. Everything all right?
- Good morning and all that.
[chatting inaudibly]
[ominous music playing]
I know you were behind the shooting.
Don't worry. I'm not here to get revenge.
I came to give you a warning.
You need to leave my brother out of this.
Dídac's staying in this school
no matter what.
Understand?
Okay. But I will not allow him
to keep seeing my daughter.
I don't like that they're together either,
but it's their life.
[ominous music building]
[ominous music fades]
[Isa] I know.
It's not exactly the most important,
but it's also very important.
Yeah, but we can't force anything, Isa.
Your body's been through a lot of trauma.
And it's reacting.
It's telling you
it just needs a little rest.
That's all it is, all right?
Don't worry.
[footsteps approaching]
What's up, bebés?
Kiddo, would you give me
and my daughter a minute?
See you in a bit. [kisses]
Why're you here? What do you want?
To finalize the details
of the race with Virginia.
Well, and also
to bring you a little something.
Nothing fancy.
I want every single person
at the racecourse
to know who my daughter is.
[sighs] So, bribery.
That's why you're here.
Which of our horses
do you want competing in the race?
No.
- Oh, sweetheart-
- [Isa] No. Seriously, no.
- Honey, that mare is the best one we have.
- Do you hear yourself?
That's literally why I'm against it.
It'd be risky for her. She's ancient.
The trip from Ibiza
will be too much for her.
Don't you get it?
She's family. You don't care about that?
You'd put her through it?
See? This is exactly why I can't bring you
into the family business.
Horses, my dear,
are also part of the business.
Business always comes first, right?
Oh, you're really throwing off
the whole vibe right now.
- Change it up for Mommy.
- No, I'm not doing a thing.
I'm not going to the race.
And I swear, if anything happens to her,
you will never see me again
in your fucking life.
- [footsteps fade]
- [somber music playing]
[Sara sighs]
[breathing shakily]
[panting]
[door unlocks, opens]
[keys jangle]
- [Sara exhales]
- [door closes]
[music fades]
[footsteps approaching]
Hey.
You didn't go to school?
No, I wasn't feeling well.
What're you doing here?
Uh, nothing. I forgot a few documents
for the race live stream for Virginia.
And then you'll be heading out?
Um, yeah.
Hey, you know what?
I'll email them to her
and set up a call with her this afternoon.
So I can take care of you.
No, Raúl, don't piss off Virginia.
She's my principal.
Besides, I'm heading out.
- Thought you weren't feeling well.
- Yeah, you're right.
I was feeling sick, but I'm fine now.
I just needed
to skip my first class today.
[somber music playing]
- I'm fine, honestly.
- Are you sure?
Mm-hmm. I'm gonna get dressed.
[somber music building]
[indistinct chatter]
- [music fades]
- [phone chimes]
NEW MESSAGE
I NEED TO BE ALONE, BUT I CAN'T.
I FEEL TRAPPED
[woman] Sara.
Yeah?
You underperformed
on the physical exam, and it was graded.
Yeah. My fault.
I'll do better.
You seem lost lately.
What's that rash on your arm?
Nothing. Allergies.
Seems like a pretty big reaction.
What're you allergic to?
A bunch of things.
There's a lot I'm allergic to.
Jessica, I'll see you later.
I'm running late.
[somber music resumes]
[music fades slowly]
[Joel] I don't understand
why you accepted this app position thing
when you wanted
nothing to do with Las Encinas.
Well, because money
and experience for a résumé.
Or was it so that you can spy on me?
[scoffs, sighs]
Or keep you safe.
I trust you, okay?
- But this school can really fuck you up.
- This again?
Can't you see how fucked up this is?
Look, Omar. I'm not you, okay?
I'm not you, and I'm not your friends.
I'm Joel,
and I wanna enjoy this opportunity.
[sighs] I'm just worried about you, babe.
[Joel] But I don't need a father.
What I need Is a boyfriend who's happy
something good's happened to me.
Who trusts in me, who gives me space,
and who doesn't cling like a barnacle,
trying to fucking control me.
Fuck.
[unsettling music playing]
[Omar sighs]
[exhales sharply]
[cell phone chimes]
KICK DÍDAC AND THE MOB OUT OF SCHOOL!!!
[huffs]
[unsettling music fades]
[Joel] Iván.
Uh, if me having a boyfriend
makes you uncomfortable here,
just tell me, and I'll leave the school.
[takes a deep breath] Paying for you
is the only thing that's brought me joy
since leaving the hospital.
- I'm perfectly happy just being friends.
- [sighs]
Well, then. We're still on for the race?
Of course. Can't wait.
[both sigh]
I assume Omar's coming too?
Uh, I don't think so. He's really busy.
[rhythmic music playing]
What's up?
Sonia.
Thank you.
Um, for not narcing on me
about leaking my own video.
Oh, some reverse psychology?
Do you want me to tell everyone
so you can get more attention?
[scoffs] Look, kid.
I'm being forced to be here.
I lashed out at you.
You didn't deserve that.
Oh, she's actually human after all.
So, besties? Colleagues?
Okay, cordial acquaintances.
[Sonia scoffs]
So, hey. Is the soccer player's son
really bisexual?
[indistinct chatter]
[Sonia] Are you serious?
Why? You scoping out
your next porn video target?
M'kay. So, yes.
Nah, with him,
I'd do cute, coupley videos, you know?
Like showing off a rich,
handsome, sexy guy on my arm.
Hey, and he's an orphan too.
Pfft. No mother-in-law?
That's the dream, right there.
[Sonia] You're describing him
like a trophy.
No, not a trophy.
The trophy.
Wow. To think I kinda liked you
when we met.
Girl, do whatever you want.
But your work is cut out for you.
[chuckles] Wanna bet on it?
Because I don't run from a challenge.
Plus, the tougher the challenge,
the more turned on I get.
Another way to seek outside validation.
Babe, you're a therapist's wet dream.
[indistinct chatter]
[Isa] What's going on?
The dirty looks. Fuckin' sick of it.
Yeah.
Why don't we cut a few classes?
[horse neighs]
And so, let me introduce you to Amazona.
[Dídac] Hi, Amazona. How are you?
Hello, my love.
- [Dídac] Didn't know you were into horses.
- I'm obsessed.
I grew up with horses in Ibiza.
She's my favorite.
My mom and I adopted her.
She wanted her to be mine, but I said no.
That way, Amazona has two moms.
I credit her with helping my mom
and I grow a bit closer.
That is, until my mom
decided to make her race.
That's when all the problems started.
Because I am completely
against her racing.
But you know how it is.
When she sees a business opportunity,
Roberta doesn't care about anything else.
The last time Amazona competed, she fell.
It's a miracle nothing happened to her.
I didn't think I'd survive.
Well, if you don't want her
to keep racing, let's kidnap Amazona.
Secretly whisk her away to some sanctuary.
It would have to be before the race.
But we can only get in here with a pass.
Your mother should have one.
She's the owner. Yeah?
Yeah.
Then I guess
we'll have to get it from her.
Thanks, Dídac.
- [ "The Hills" by Sol Oosel playing]
- [horses neigh]
Hello, all you beautiful people.
We're here at this spectacular racetrack,
where we're about
to celebrate Las Encinas' charity race.
All this, for an incredibly good cause.
Fundraising the exchange scholarships
between the best schools
of the Excellentia Academic Global League
in Europe and Africa.
You're not gonna want to miss it,
so stay tuned.
[energetic Italian song continues]
We need to start doing these things
together on camera, our live streams.
They're gonna catch on.
But you do you.
[sighs] I'll go find Virginia.
♪ I'm gonna fire up the hills now ♪
♪ The fire's gonna sail into the sky ♪
[indistinct chatter]
♪ I'm gonna fire up the hills now ♪
♪ The fire's gonna… ♪
Go on. Don't worry.
Go on. I'll see you later.
Hello there.
Everything good?
- You look beautiful.
- [Isa] Mm.
[energetic Italian song continues]
[mouthing]
[Roberta] The ambassador came after all.
Oh, his wife's put on weight.
I need your pass to the stables.
- I'm going-
- Why do you want it?
Because I want to give
a good luck kiss to Amazona.
Oh, honey, don't.
You'll make her nervous. No, no.
You'll see her after. Don't be a pain.
[man on PA] The second race
of the Las Encinas…
[mouthing]
[man on PA] …is as follows.
Pichi, Hills, Babel…
- Dídac, how are you?
- I'm great.
You?
I read some nasty comments
on the app against you and your family.
There were a few, yeah.
But it is what it is.
Well, if you need to talk about anything,
like about how you're feeling,
the classmates, your family…
Why my family?
I meant your family or anything else.
I'm here, okay?
You'll never catch me judging.
All right. Thanks.
[tense music playing]
[Dídac] Pau, honestly, I don't understand
what the fuck you're doing here, man.
Dídac, I was invited here.
I'm flesh and blood, dude.
Well, I'd prefer it if you left.
You've never looked at me
with such disgust.
Please just leave.
You're making a mistake, kiddo.
[tense music building]
- [tense music fades]
- [indistinct, excited chatter]
Oof. This shit goes
to your head, huh? [laughs]
Yeah, it really does.
- I'll go get more.
- [Iván] Okay.
[indistinct announcements on PA]
[Iván sighs]
I'm sorry for what you've been through.
- Pardon?
- The hit-and-run.
And the thing with your father too.
The moms at school, we talk.
And well, you can guess.
Well, anyway, I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Your name's Iván, right?
Iván.
Oh, what a beautiful name.
I've always loved it.
My name's Carmen.
Mwah. Mwah.
Just Carmen.
Nice to meet you.
So, how is everything?
Well, not that great, as you know.
Oh shit, how rude of me.
- No. You're good.
- I put my foot in my mouth.
Look, I actually have
a friend waiting for me, so…
He was a great human, your father.
Did you know him?
I read about him.
And I read about
what he did for you guys too.
Who's "us guys"?
For the gays.
God rest his soul.
God loves you, no matter what they say.
Don't forget.
It's amazing.
You're the spitting image of him.
- I'd say you're more handsome, really.
- [Iván chuckles]
Mom, why not try hanging out
with guys your own age?
- See you around. Nice meeting you.
- Yeah. Ciao.
- Ciao, ciao.
- Ciao. [chuckles]
[Chloe] Mom, he could be your son.
- [Carmen] What?
- What do you mean, "what"?
I saw the way
you looked at him and smiled.
- Hot, rich? I know what you're doing.
- You thought I was hitting on him?
No. But I won't risk you embarrassing me.
You need to stay away from him.
[sighs] Look. That wasn't the plan, dear.
And even if I wanted to,
he's gay, just like his father.
[scoffs] You stay away. I mean it.
[announcer on PA] The third race
will start in five minutes.
With number one, White Coast.
- [indistinct chatter]
- [announcer continues indistinctly]
[girl] Later.
[Raúl] I don't care what we agreed.
So we're working for free?
It's a collaboration.
- [Raúl] Okay. Understood.
- That's what I'm saying.
[Virginia] I'm sorry
to disappoint you, Raúl.
[Raúl] No, that's okay. Thanks. Okay?
Sorry for any confusion.
Well, fuck this whole thing!
- Raúl, what's the matter?
- Yeah, fuck Virginia!
- Keep your voice down, Raúl.
- That bitch won't pay us for the stream.
Yeah. She asked me as a favor. I told-
Yeah, and you accepted it for free?
When we're both fucking broke?
We'll lose the apartment now.
- Wait. Why didn't you tell me this?
- I did.
I said if you split up with me,
you'd destroy our bank account.
Well, there. I said if you
and I didn't appear as a happy couple,
we'd lose followers
and a ton of brand deals.
I fucking told you! Didn't I tell you?
You happy?
Realize your fuckin' tantrums
have consequences, you fucking child!
- [exhales]
- [tense music playing]
[music fades]
[Chloe] Please excuse my mother.
She can be super annoying.
Nah, you're good.
She wasn't bothering me at all.
You're uncomfortable.
Because you recognize me
from the video, right?
What video?
Please. You haven't watched?
Mm, no.
Well, I'll send it right now.
In fact, I'll send you
a better one that you'll like.
[cell phone chimes]
There you are.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
Ciao.
[cell phone beeps]
- [both moaning loudly]
- [Iván gasps]
[crowd murmurs]
[Iván chuckles softly]
I couldn't find you. [chuckles]
Wait, so I took so long
that you came here to order for yourself?
[chuckles] Here you go.
- [Iván] Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Cheers?
Cheers.
[cell phone vibrating]
- [somber music playing]
- [vibrating continues]
[sighs] One sec.
[somber music fades]
Nothin'. Eric's disappeared.
And my parents will flip out
if he doesn't come.
[guy scoffs]
THE SPIDER SOCIAL CENTER #WEARESTAYING
Forget that shit. Today, it's uniform.
Tomorrow, it's something else.
[Rocío] I absolutely detest uniforms.
And most rules, really.
Yeah, said the domesticated sheep.
The best way to change the system
is from the inside out.
[scoffs] That so? With what?
A really angry tweet?
A little ribbon on your lapel?
Yo. My friend
from the courthouse just called.
Riot police will be back tonight.
Those fuckin' pigs.
I can get them to stop the eviction.
Eric, listen to me.
You? Okay, how?
Put your suit on,
come back, and I'll show you how.
[Joel] Well, I came out of the closet
to my parents.
And they kicked me out of the house.
[Iván] Wow. That still happens?
For, um… for a while,
I slept in parks and, um,
and ate wherever I could.
Until I came to Madrid
and went to an association
to ask for help.
Omar, he worked there.
And so, out of the blue,
without knowing him,
he let me live with him.
- [gentle music playing]
- I don't know.
I've always been convinced
that we were meant to be together.
And when we met, we…
we were both pretty much at rock bottom.
[Joel] Me because of my parent shit.
And Omar,
due to a really serious depression
over, I don't know…
something he won't tell me.
[Omar breathing heavily]
[Joel] It was so bad
that he almost did something crazy.
[music intensifies]
[exhales]
But, y'know?
Together, we made our way through it,
and fell madly in love with each other.
[Iván sighs]
Although, now I'm not sure
if it was codependence
or it really was love.
[music fades slowly]
How long ago did you start dating?
Almost a year, I guess. Why?
Samuel.
Who's Samuel? Omar's ex?
[gentle music playing]
No, his best friend,
who also went to Las Encinas.
He died in his arms.
[tense music playing]
[breathing shakily]
- [faucet squeaks]
- [water runs]
- [faucet squeaks closed]
- [exhales]
[breathing shakily]
[sighs]
[tense music building]
[door opens]
[Joel] Omar?
[door closes]
Omar?
- [music fades slowly]
- [footsteps approaching]
[sighs]
You should've told me
about your friend Samuel.
[gentle music playing]
[sighs] The hardest part
is that I could've saved him.
If I hadn't kept him at arm's length.
If I had just kept an eye on him.
[sighs] Fuck.
[sobs]
[gently] Come here. Come here.
[Omar sniffles, sobbing]
[softly] It's all right.
[Joel] It's okay.
- [sniffles]
- [Omar continues crying]
[excited chatter]
[announcer on PA] All bets are now final.
She's got a death grip on that handbag.
[announcer on PA] The sixth
and final race will start in 30 minutes.
Oh fuckin' hell.
[indistinct chatter]
Nico, having fun?
Son, your cousin's out of control.
It's his nature.
You need to accept that.
Look who's coming.
["Marie Antoinette" by Boyfriend playing]
♪ Livin' fabulous ♪
♪ Livin' lavish ♪
♪ Livin' stylish ♪
♪ Flamboyant ♪
♪ Extravagant ♪
♪ Livin' lavish ♪
♪ Yeah, I'm a bad bitch ♪
♪ I'mma roll up in a golden carriage ♪
♪ Pulled by six white stallions ♪
♪ That match what I'm wearin' ♪
- ♪ I walk in, and my status is apparent ♪
- This way.
♪ And I fan myself with feathers
While I yawn in Paris ♪
♪ My hair and my nails
And the heels that I'm on… ♪
[Rocío] That's my mom. She's a judge.
And living proof the system
can be changed from the inside out.
♪ My jacket, my sheets
And my curtains, chiffon ♪
♪ Too much of a good thing
Won't do me harm ♪
- ♪ I want 100 commas on my check ♪
- ♪ Ching, ching ♪
♪ I wanna spend about a million dollars
In one breath ♪
♪ Wanna go so hard ♪
- ♪ I might just lose my head ♪
- ♪ Head ♪
♪ I wanna live expensive
Like Marie Antoinette ♪
♪ Livin' fabulous ♪
♪ Livin' lavish… ♪
TO IVÁN: DID YOU LIKE MY VIDEO?
♪ Extravagant ♪
♪ Livin' fabulous ♪
♪ Livin' lavish ♪
- ♪ Yeah, I'm a bad bitch ♪
- [song ends]
[announcer speaking indistinctly on PA]
[speaking inaudibly]
How is the challenge going?
He's ripe for the picking.
How's yours going?
I saw how you looked at Nico.
[tense music playing]
[sighs]
So she blew you off?
She wanted to dance, she said.
I adore him, but I'm sick of suffering.
I feel best when I'm with her.
And you apologized to her?
I can't stay away, no matter what I do.
Nico's my addiction.
Mm, yeah.
I'll be right back.
Well, time to test your resolve
because he's heading this way.
You better not leave me
alone with him. Don't you dare.
[Nico] What's up?
- Hi there.
- [Sonia] Hi.
Well, then, um, I should be going.
Be back later.
Chloe, hold on. Wait. [sighs]
[tense music fades]
[cell phone chimes]
Iván, thank you
for telling Joel about Samuel
and opening the line of communication.
We patched things up.
[gentle music playing]
By the way, I hear that Patrick
is the prime suspect in your hit-and-run.
You know as well as I do that's absurd.
He wouldn't do that.
In case you needed a reminder.
[footsteps approaching]
Hey, handsome.
Hello.
What a face.
You never texted back.
Didn't like the video?
I did. It was nice.
Iván, listen.
Trust me, I've seen that face
many times before.
But, you know what?
I'm an expert at curing heartbreak.
So look, I mean…
A little taste of this,
and you won't remember who broke it.
[tense music playing]
[Nico] "I'm really into bondage."
"I get all kinds of turned on
when my wife spanks me." [laughs]
"I'm telling you, he's like a horny goat."
"Look, I spank him like this. Bam, bam.
And baby, he's like a bitch in heat."
[gasps] Oh shit.
We've been made. [giggles]
[both laugh]
I'm kinda starving.
I'll be back. Don't leave.
Can I take this off your hands?
[giggles] Thank you.
[Sonia] Mm.
- That's actually pretty good.
- [Nico] Mm-hmm.
[both laugh]
I really missed this, you know?
Hangin' out, laughin' with you.
I wish I could go back in time
and erase all the damage I did.
But… what's done is done.
So there's no chance for redemption?
'Cause I could think of a way.
["No Cover" by Catnapp playing]
[Sonia giggles]
- [moans]
- [door closes]
♪ I never said ♪
- ♪ That you could be my cover ♪
- [Sonia laughs]
♪ You shouldn't miss me
When you got another ♪
♪ The shit's so heavy
But I'm holding on ♪
♪ It's hard to keep my face up
You ain't got inside me any place, fuck ♪
♪ It feels like it is coming out… ♪
[Chloe laughs]
[Iván and Chloe panting]
[Chloe] Shh, shh, shh, shh, shh!
- Let's play a little bit, yeah?
- [kissing]
[Chloe] Wow. For a Brazilian,
you'd think you'd be better at sambaing.
[Iván sighs] I mean,
maybe today isn't the day.
This happens sometimes.
[Chloe] Don't worry.
Just close your eyes and enjoy the show.
[breathing heavily] All right. Wait.
Mm. Um, I'm not in the mood, okay?
It's not you.
Wow. You really are gonna be
my biggest challenge, aren't you?
Chloe, open the door.
[Chloe] Mom?
Open up.
I need to speak with you right now.
- [Chloe] Mom, not right now. I'm kinda-
- Dammit. I said open up, Chloe!
No. No, no, no. Iván!
Iván! [scoffs]
You're so jealous,
you'd cockblock your daughter?
- You're fucking serious?
- You've got it wrong.
- Stay away from Iván. Trust me on this.
- [scoffs] Go fuck yourself.
[Carmen] Hey!
Don't talk to me like that! Okay?
Wait! Wait!
[indistinct chatter]
[Carmen] Chloe, listen to me, please.
Chloe, wait.
Chloe, please.
Chloe, I said stop!
What? What do you want?
- He's your brother.
- [Chloe] What?
Wow, Mom.
You are seriously so fucking batshit
that you'd make up anything just to win.
- That's it, isn't it?
- No. He's your brother.
- That's why we came.
- [tense music playing]
[announcer on PA] Attention. For reasons
beyond the organization's control,
the last race has been suspended.
- What's going on?
- What happened?
- I'm sorry.
- [Isa] What?
- [foreman] Someone poisoned her.
- [quietly] What?
- No.
- [foreman] There was nothing we could do.
Why are you here? Go.
Get outta here, you piece of shit.
[sobs] Mom.
Who do you think would've done this
to your sweet Amazona?
[Isa crying] No.
Your brother won't stop
till he tears our lives apart.
[Isa continues crying]
[Dídac sobbing]
[crying]
Dídac.
- [Dídac continues crying]
- Hey. What's goin' on?
I'm so fuckin' sick of my family.
- [tense music playing]
- Bunch of fuckin' murderers.
[tense music building]
[Isa continues sobbing]
[music fades]
[Sara breathing shakily]
[unsettling music playing]
- [music fades]
- I said I'm good. Really. I'm fine.
Listen, are you having problems at home?
I know all about the ups and downs
you're having with Raúl.
I mean, me
and millions of other people too.
And about his little habit
of crying on the Internet
to guilt you into getting back together.
It's a textbook case. I know the type.
Jessica, who asked you
to butt into my life?
[gentle music playing]
I'm saying this
'cause I've been through the same thing.
I don't know what you mean by "thing."
There isn't anything going on
at home or anywhere.
I couldn't see a way
out of it then either.
But there is.
[Jessica] Of course,
you have to find it yourself.
Not wait for it to appear.
[music grows somber]
[Patrick on recording]
But for my wish to be fulfilled,
my only option is to disappear.
Or that's what I'm told.
["Fixe" by Ora Cogan playing]
[Patrick] So,
until we see each other again,
I love you. [sobs]
I love you so much, Iván. [sniffles]
I've always loved you, and I always will.
DO YOU WANT TO DELETE THIS MESSAGE
FROM PATRICK?
["Fixe" continues playing]
I think the guy who ran me over
had to have been at the masquerade.
I didn't see anything.
Wish I would've.
You want us to take Iván in?
As long as he's still living alone,
he won't stop obsessing over it.
Until he eventually figures it all out.
But if he's here,
we at least have him under control.
But what would I do
with my home if I leave?
[Sara] Well, you rent it.
Or sell it. Your house is a booby trap.
As long as you're living there alone,
you'll feel like the walls
are caving in on you.
Trapping you with the ghosts
of your father, Patrick, the hit-and-run.
You'll never move on.
Yeah, no. This is our place.
[Sara] Yeah, but we're losing it anyway,
aren't we?
If we take in a roommate who isn't broke,
he could help us pay the rent,
and it'd give us time to keep our home
and find new clients,
which would help us get back on our feet.
You've gotta trust me, babe.
[Iván] You're right.
But if I leave my house,
I have no clue where I'd live.
["Fixe" fades slowly]
[cell phone chimes]
SARAUL ARE FAKE AF
[sighs]
Go get dressed. You'll be late.
I'm quitting school.
[Omar scoffs]
'Cause, um… [scoffs]
I don't know.
I don't want you to suffer for my sake.
[Omar sighs]
Would you really do that for me?
Well, yeah.
[gentle music playing]
Look, you…
are my top priority.
[Omar sighs]
I'm the one with the problem.
So I should quit the job.
[sighs] But isn't this good experience
for you?
And the money.
What money? The pay's utter shit.
And the app doesn't work.
They only use it for trolling.
And to get over my trauma,
I gotta let you fly.
And stay away from there.
[sighs] Thank you.
I promise you, I won't let it change me.
[Omar sighs]
- [knocking on door]
- [door opens]
Luis, you got a minute?
Of course.
[cell phone chimes]
MY LIFE IS HELL. I CAN'T SEE A WAY OUT.
I NEED TO GET OUT OF THE WAY.
What's the matter?
[tense music building]
Look at that. Eventually,
someone was gonna ask for help.
Well then, let's help them.
I'M HERE TO LISTEN TO YOU
AND HELP YOU WITH WHATEVER YOU NEED.
TALK TO ME.
[tense music swells]
[Omar sighs deeply]
[music ends abruptly]
[somber instrumental music playing]